<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Leonardo Henrique</title><link>https://henrikkudesu.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Leonardo Henrique</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://henrikkudesu.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contributing to Social Causes as a Developer</title><link>https://henrikkudesu.github.io/posts/test/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://henrikkudesu.github.io/posts/test/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>I’m writing this post especially for developers at the beginning of their careers, but it can also be valuable for professionals at any level.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Around the world, there are countless non-profit social organizations, such as NGOs, Civil Society Organizations, Charity Associations, and other groups working in various fields. They play an essential role in society, helping minorities, underprivileged groups, the environment, war victims, people with disabilities, elderly individuals in vulnerable situations, isolated rural communities, and even promoting public education and healthcare. Many times, we want to contribute to these causes, but the sheer number of organizations available makes it hard to decide which one to support. However, the solution is simpler than it seems: just choose a cause that resonates with you and make your contribution, even if it’s small. That alone will be enough to create a positive impact. I believe that, as citizens, we have a responsibility to lend a hand to those in need.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Small Projects That Help Improve Your Programming Skills</title><link>https://henrikkudesu.github.io/posts/small-projects-to-improve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://henrikkudesu.github.io/posts/small-projects-to-improve/</guid><description>&lt;p>Practicing with real-world projects is one of the best ways to enhance your programming skills. Frontend Mentor is a great platform that provides design challenges based on real-world scenarios, helping developers sharpen their skills in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In &lt;a href="https://github.com/henrikkudesu/frontendmentor-challenges" target="_blank">my repository&lt;/a>, I have completed various projects that helped me improve my coding abilities. Here are some examples:&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="-3-column-preview-card-component">📌 3-Column Preview Card Component&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>This project focuses on building a responsive layout using CSS Flexbox and Grid to arrange content in three columns.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>